[Music]
this market life in Mindanao I was the
eldest child I have three more siblings
in the early age I have to help my
parents in providing for our family so
via Maya who makes pose
seventeen actually I started selling
when I was eight years old and was
selling ice water and then I became a
working student just to provide for our
daily needs and to also share that to
all my siblings and my family what do
you base it needs about that life is so
hard
so real are some sources and resources
well that wasn't so wrong my god I have
asked myself what's with money but I
shall be available tomorrow political I
have been away with our youth oven
Imperial yeah you knew karate in the
ghee in question a problem so I begin my
quest because of that question paladin
mention of a poor man masa lucky me
aluminium a sweetener and
it was a little fire under my butt in
successful defense of the Eco element in
you is happening because they started
with cold murky commodity like that but
then Sahaba ascension in with my strong
belief that I am me for this career the
leg on the Sumita a boy I just continued
to attend trainings biomedical data then
is you trust without trust them and I'm
oh so much struggle your name fun
designing the process the sovereign here
of familiar well I remember that me
their target see nobody knew on that
side
so the extra of Ganesha then is when
Allah Masha Allah he neither windows
immediately restarted of course they
came from Mindanao that was in my
classmates for the sake of memory so
Paragon I started with gold market they
must not ask you Neverland rejection
sorry I overcome all the challenges when
I started in this business way number
one technical industry means because
they I have to equip myself with the
knowledge and skills para uma Lena
karate pupusas and to explain the
products to make values no opportunity
make me nervous advise the mama
successful not into saying the tsunami
so now what would a relative Selena
and number three that again perseverance
in the offices of God I was staying here
no matter what
and if my encounter mouth challenges
that's just easy side of this business
but if I will continue to learn from you
more and more when life right now it's
amazing
can I be it's possible that everything
let's not be put a little of everything
is that it's really joy and Hindi lunch
I enjoy because I have this per year but
joy also because I was able to take good
care of my relationships with my family
with my friends number three also with
the finances that they have right now
compared to my point
so now you're talking again and I am
enjoying a limited income because of
this opportunity I travel around the
room and it's all for free the entire
human experience or not bliss inside my
heart because of this career Sabra dot a
paraphilic o11 family 40 years of bad
habit bottoms level cada mañana de nada
mas jabo
join life to the fulness my mission is
to save as many Filipinos as they can
through financial planning and provide
the next generation a better future
at night I feel that it is my calling
also to share the power of financial
planning to each Filipino families but I
am definitely Papa - Amana enough Madame
tour next generation Nutella I say it's
time for us to break that chain of
poverty now I want to grow my team
because you [__] [__] I am going them I
will not lay beside I need people who
are passionate enough who wanted to help
more people also to do this work
together with me
[Music]
you